A Guide to the Governor Gerald L. Baliles Executive Papers, 1986-1990
Library of Virginia
- Series III. 1988 (accession 33702)
  - Sub-Series E: Cabinet
    - Department of Conservation and Historic Resources (part one) (Box 127, Folder 1)
    - Department of Conservation and Historic Resources (part two) (Box 127, Folder 2)
    - Department of Parks and Recreation (Box 127, Folder 3)
    - Department of Waste Management (Box 127, Folder 4)
    - Marine Resources Commission (Box 127, Folder 5)
    - State Air Pollution Control Board (Box 127, Folder 6)
    - State Water Control Board (Box 127, Folder 7)
    - Virginia Resources Authority (Box 127, Folder 8)
    - E.6 - Secretary of Natural Resources - Natural Resources Topics
    - False Cape State Park (Box 127, Folder 9)
    - Hunting and Fishing License Fee (Box 127, Folder 10)
    - Jackson River (Box 128, Folder 1)
    - Lake Gaston (Box 128, Folder 2)
    - Manassas National Battlefield (part one) (Box 128, Folder 3)
    - Manassas National Battlefield (part two) (Box 128, Folder 4)
    - School of the Bay (Box 128, Folder 5)
    - Shamrock Marathon (Box 128, Folder 6)
    - Thunderbird site (Box 128, Folder 7)
    - E.7 - Secretary of Transportation and Public Safety
    - Correspondence sent and/or copied to Governor's Office, 1988 December 30-September 20 (Box 128, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence sent and/or copied to Governor's Office, 1988 September 9-June 21 (Box 128, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence sent and/or copied to Governor's Office, 1988 June 20-March 10 (Box 128, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence sent and/or copied to Governor's Office, 1988 March 8-February 5 (Box 129, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence sent and/or copied to Governor's Office, 1988 February 4-January 5 (Box 129, Folder 2)
    - Deputy Secretary of Transportation and Public Safety, Correspondence and Memorandums sent and/or copied to Governor's Office, 1988 (Box 129, Folder 3)
    - Governor's Correspondence, 1988 December 29-October 13 (Box 129, Folder 4)
    - Governor's Correspondence, 1988 September 30-January 4 (Box 129, Folder 5)
    - E.7 - Secretary of Transportation and Public Safety - State Agencies
    - Alcoholic Beverage Control Board (Box 129, Folder 6)
    - Department of Aviation (Box 129, Folder 7)
    - Board of Corrections - Virginia Parole Board (Box 129, Folder 8)
    - Department of Corrections (part one) (Box 130, Folder 1)
    - Department of Corrections (part two) (Box 130, Folder 2)
    - Department of Corrections - Prison Overcrowding (Box 130, Folder 3)
    - Department of Criminal Justice (Box 130, Folder 4)
    - Department of Emergency Services (Box 130, Folder 5)
    - Department of Fire Programs (Box 130, Folder 6)
    - Department of Military Affairs (Box 130, Folder 7)
    - Department of Motor Vehicles (part one) (Box 130, Folder 8)
    - Department of Motor Vehicles (part two) (Box 130, Folder 9)
    - Department of Motor Vehicles (part three) (Box 130, Folder 10)
    - Department of State Police (part one) (Box 131, Folder 1)
    - Department of State Police (part two) (Box 131, Folder 2)
    - Department of State Police (part three) (Box 131, Folder 3)
    - Department of Transportation (part one) (Box 131, Folder 4)
    - Department of Transportation (part two) (Box 131, Folder 5)
    - Department of Transportation (part three) (Box 131, Folder 6)
    - Department of Transportation (part four) (Box 131, Folder 7)
    - Department of Transportation (part five) (Box 132, Folder 1)
    - Department of Transportation (part six) (Box 132, Folder 2)
    - Department of Transportation (part seven) (Box 132, Folder 3)
    - Department of Transportation - Route 29 (Box 132, Folder 4)
    - Department of Transportation - Route 58 (Box 132, Folder 5)
    - Department of Transportation - Route 288 (Box 132, Folder 6)
    - Department of Transportation - Washington Bypass Study (Box 132, Folder 7)
    - Virginia Port Authority (Box 132, Folder 8)
    - E.7 - Secretary of Transportation and Public Safety - Topics
    - National Guard (Box 133, Folder 1)
    - Nopwasky, Gladys (Box 133, Folder 2)
    - "Explore" Project - Roanoke River Parkway (Box 133, Folder 3)
  - Sub-Series F: General Assembly
    - 1988 Legislation, General Correspondence (Box 133, Folder 4)
    - House Bills, General Correspondence (Box 133, Folder 5)
    - Senate Bills, General Correspondence (Box 133, Folder 6)
    - General Assembly - Membership List for 1988 (Box 133, Folder 7)
    - Clerk of the House of Delegates, Correspondence (Box 133, Folder 8)
    - House of Delegates, Correspondence, A-C (Box 133, Folder 9)
    - House of Delegates, Correspondence, D-H (Box 133, Folder 10)
    - House of Delegates, Correspondence, J-O (Box 134, Folder 1)
    - House of Delegates, Correspondence, P-W (Box 134, Folder 2)
    - Clerk of the Senate, Correspondence (Box 134, Folder 3)
    - Senate Correspondence, A-E (Box 134, Folder 4)
    - Senate Correspondence, F-H (Box 134, Folder 5)
    - Senate Correspondence, L-W (Box 134, Folder 6)
  - Sub-Series G: Secretary of the Commonwealth
    - Actual Appointments (Box 135, Folder 1)
  - Sub-Series H: Legislative
    - Auditor of Public Accounts (Box 135, Folder 2)
    - Division of Legislative Services (Box 135, Folder 3)
  - Sub-Series I: Attorney General
    - Department of Law - Division of War Veterans' Claims (Box 135, Folder 4)
  - Sub-Series J: Judicial
    - General (Box 135, Folder 5)
    - Virginia State Bar (Box 135, Folder 6)
  - Sub-Series K: Independent State Agencies
    - Industrial Commission of Virginia - Department of Workman's Compensation (Box 135, Folder 7)
    - State Corporation Commission - General (Box 135, Folder 8)
    - State Corporation Commission - Bureau of Financial Institutions (Box 135, Folder 9)
    - State Corporation Commission - Bureau of Insurance (Box 135, Folder 10)
    - State Corporation Commission - Division of Energy Regulation (Box 135, Folder 11)
    - State Lottery Department (part one) (Box 135, Folder 12)
    - State Lottery Department (part two) (Box 135, Folder 13)
  - Sub-Series L: Lt. Governor
    - L. Douglas Wilder (Box 136, Folder 1)
  - Sub-Series M: Virginia Liaison Office
    - Correspondence and Memorandums, 1988 (Box 136, Folder 2)
  - Sub-Series N: United States Government
    - Senate - General (Box 136, Folder 3)
    - Senate - John W. Warner (part one) (Box 136, Folder 4)
    - Senate - John W. Warner (part two) (Box 136, Folder 5)
    - Senate - Paul S. Trible (Box 136, Folder 6)
    - House of Representatives - General (Box 136, Folder 7)
    - Virginia Congressional Delegation - General (Box 136, Folder 8)
    - House of Representatives - Herbert Bateman, 1st District (Box 136, Folder 9)
    - House of Representatives - Owen Picket, 2nd District (Box 136, Folder 10)
    - House of Representatives - Thomas Bliley, 3rd District (Box 136, Folder 11)
    - House of Representatives - Norman Sisisky, 4th District (Box 136, Folder 12)
    - House of Representatives - Lewis F. Payne, Jr., 5th District (Box 136, Folder 13)
    - House of Representatives - James Olin, 6th District (Box 136, Folder 14)
    - House of Representatives - D. Frank Slaughter, 7th District (Box 136, Folder 15)
    - House of Representatives - Stanford Parris, 8th District (Box 136, Folder 16)
    - House of Representatives - Frederick Boucher, 9th District (Box 136, Folder 17)
    - House of Representatives - Frank Wolf, 10th District (Box 136, Folder 18)
    - Department of Agriculture (Box 137, Folder 1)
    - Department of the Army (Box 137, Folder 2)
    - Department of the Army - Corps of Engineers (Box 137, Folder 3)
    - Department of Commerce (Box 137, Folder 4)
    - Department of Defense (Box 137, Folder 5)
    - Department of Education (Box 137, Folder 6)
    - Department of Energy (Box 137, Folder 7)
    - Department of Health and Human Services (Box 137, Folder 8)
    - Department of Housing and Urban Development (Box 137, Folder 9)
    - Department of Immigration and Naturalization (Box 137, Folder 10)
    - Department of the Interior (Box 137, Folder 11)
    - Department of Justice (Box 138, Folder 1)
    - Department of Labor (Box 138, Folder 2)
    - Department of the Navy (Box 138, Folder 3)
    - Department of the Navy, EMPRESS II (Electromagnetic Pulse Radiation Environment Simulator for Ships), 1988 (Box 138, Folder 4)
    - Department of State (Box 138, Folder 5)
    - Department of Transportation (Box 138, Folder 6)
    - Department of Transportation - Coast Guard (Box 138, Folder 7)
    - Department of the Treasury (Box 138, Folder 8)
    - Environmental Protection Agency (EPA) (Box 138, Folder 9)
    - Federal Emergency Management Agency (FEMA) (Box 138, Folder 10)
    - General (Box 138, Folder 11)
    - General Services Administration (Box 138, Folder 12)
    - Office of Technology Assessment (Box 138, Folder 13)
    - Postal Service (Box 138, Folder 14)
    - Small Business Administration (Box 138, Folder 15)
    - Social Security Administration (Box 138, Folder 16)
    - U.S. Savings Bonds (Box 138, Folder 17)
    - Veterans Administration (Box 138, Folder 18)
    - White House (Box 138, Folder 19)
- Series IV: 1989 (accession 33707)
  Notable records include Governor's briefing material for Virginia Military Advisory Commission meeting on 1 December 1989 including schedule, agenda, and preparation material (Cabinet, Secretary of Transportation and Public Safety, Box 182, Folder 4); monthly status reports to Governor Baliles on Virginia lottery (Independent State Agencies, State Lottery, Box 186, Folder 2); and Governor's briefing material on the national Education Summit with President George H.W. Bush, held at Charlottesville, Virginia, on 27-28 September 1989.
  - Sub-Series A: General Correspondence
    - Clean Air (Box 139, Folder 1)
    - Flag Requests (Box 139, Folder 2)
    - Friendship Force (Box 139, Folder 3)
    - Greekfest - Virginia Beach (Box 139, Folder 4)
    - School Children's Letters - Samples (Box 139, Folder 5)
    - Scouts - Boys/Eagles/Girls (part one) (Box 139, Folder 6)
    - Scouts - Boys/Eagles/Girls (part two) (Box 139, Folder 7)
    - Scouts - Boys/Eagles/Girls (part three) (Box 140, Folder 1)
    - Unanswered, Samples of (Box 140, Folder 2)
    - United States Holocaust Memorial (Box 140, Folder 3)
  - Sub-Series B: Associations
    - General (Box 140, Folder 4)
    - Council of State Governments (Box 140, Folder 5)
    - National Governors' Association - Correspondence (Box 140, Folder 6)
    - National Governors' Association - Publications (part one) (Box 140, Folder 7)
    - National Governors' Association - Publications (part two) (Box 140, Folder 8)
    - [See Series VI. Miscellaneous for additional National Governors' Association records.]
    - Southern Governors' Association - Correspondence (Box 141, Folder 1)
    - Southern Growth Policies Board (part one) (Box 141, Folder 2)
    - Southern Growth Policies Board (part two) (Box 141, Folder 3)
    - Southern Growth Policies Board (part three) (Box 141, Folder 4)
    - Southern States Energy Board - TVA (Box 141, Folder 5)
  - Sub-Series C: Localities
    - General (Box 141, Folder 6)
    - Cities - General (part one) (Box 141, Folder 7)
    - Cities - General (part two) (Box 142, Folder 1)
    - Counties - General (Box 142, Folder 2)
    - Towns - General (Box 142, Folder 3)
  - Sub-Series D: Governor's Office
    - Bicentennial of the United States Constitution (Box 142, Folder 4)
    - Census (part one) (Box 142, Folder 5)
    - Census (part two) (Box 142, Folder 6)
    - Congratulations - Birthday (Box 142, Folder 7)
    - Congratulations - General (part one) (Box 142, Folder 8)
    - Congratulations - General (part two) (Box 143, Folder 1)
    - Congratulations - General (part three) (Box 143, Folder 2)
    - Congratulations - General (part four) (Box 143, Folder 3)
    - Congratulations - Wedding (Box 143, Folder 4)
    - Constituent Correspondence, Robert B. Jones, Jr., Special Assistant, 1989 December 29-December 14 (Box 143, Folder 5)
    - Constituent Correspondence, Robert B. Jones, Jr., Special Assistant, 1989 December 13-November 30 (Box 143, Folder 6)
    - Constituent Correspondence, Robert B. Jones, Jr., Special Assistant, 1989 November 29-November 17 (Box 143, Folder 7)
    - Constituent Correspondence, Robert B. Jones, Jr., Special Assistant, 1989 November 16-October 31 (Box 144, Folder 1)
    - Constituent Correspondence, Robert B. Jones, Jr., Special Assistant, 1989 October 30-October 17 (Box 144, Folder 2)
    - Constituent Correspondence, Robert B. Jones, Jr., Special Assistant, 1989 October 16-October 3 (Box 144, Folder 3)
    - Constituent Correspondence, Robert B. Jones, Jr., Special Assistant, 1989 September 29-September 11 (Box 144, Folder 4)
    - Constituent Correspondence, Robert B. Jones, Jr., Special Assistant, 1989 September 8-August 30 (Box 144, Folder 5)
    - Constituent Correspondence, Robert B. Jones, Jr., Special Assistant, 1989 August 29-August 14 (Box 144, Folder 6)
    - Constituent Correspondence, Robert B. Jones, Jr., Special Assistant, 1989 August 11-July 28 (Box 145, Folder 1)
    - Constituent Correspondence, Robert B. Jones, Jr., Special Assistant, 1989 July 27-July 14 (Box 145, Folder 2)
    - Constituent Correspondence, Robert B. Jones, Jr., Special Assistant, 1989 July 13-June 26 (Box 145, Folder 3)
    - Constituent Correspondence, Robert B. Jones, Jr., Special Assistant, 1989 June 23-May 25 (Box 145, Folder 4)
    - Constituent Correspondence, H. Benson Dendy, III, Special Assistant, 1989 May 23-May 2 (Box 145, Folder 5)
    - Constituent Correspondence, H. Benson Dendy, III, Special Assistant, 1989 April 28-March 17 (Box 145, Folder 6)
    - Constituent Correspondence, H. Benson Dendy, III, Special Assistant, 1989 March 16-February 13 (Box 146, Folder 1)
    - Constituent Correspondence, H. Benson Dendy, III, Special Assistant, 1989 February 8-January 3 (Box 146, Folder 2)
    - Constituent Correspondence - See Also Form Letters
    - Danville Tour (Box 146, Folder 3)
    - Eastern Shore Workday (Box 146, Folder 4)
    - Get Well Letters (Box 146, Folder 5)
    - Governor's Biographical Sketch (Box 146, Folder 6)
    - Governor's Commission on Excellence in Education - Report, October 1989 (Box 146, Folder 7)
    - Governor's General Correspondence, 1989 December 29-December 18 (Box 146, Folder 8)
    - Governor's General Correspondence, 1989 December 14-November 28 (Box 146, Folder 9)
    - Governor's General Correspondence, 1989 November 27-October 25 (Box 147, Folder 1)
    - Governor's General Correspondence, 1989 October 24-September 20 (Box 147, Folder 2)
    - Governor's General Correspondence, 1989 September 19-August 11 (Box 147, Folder 3)
    - Governor's General Correspondence, 1989 August 10-July 5 (Box 147, Folder 4)
    - Governor's General Correspondence, 1989 July 3-June 5 (Box 147, Folder 5)
    - Governor's General Correspondence, 1989 June 1-April 25 (Box 147, Folder 6)
    - Governor's General Correspondence, 1989 April 24-March 22 (Box 148, Folder 1)
    - Governor's General Correspondence, 1989 March 21-February 8 (Box 148, Folder 2)
    - Governor's General Correspondence, 1989 February 7-January 3 (Box 148, Folder 3)
    - Governors, Other States (part one) (Box 148, Folder 4)
    - Governors, Other States (part two) (Box 148, Folder 5)
    - Governors, Other States (part three) (Box 148, Folder 6)
    - Grants, Block (Box 149, Folder 1)
    - Granville P. Meade Scholarship Trust (Box 149, Folder 2)
    - Greetings (Box 149, Folder 3)
    - Information and News Clippings (part one) (Box 149, Folder 4)
    - Information and News Clippings (part two) (Box 149, Folder 5)
    - Mail Trends (Box 149, Folder 6)
    - Meetings and Conventions (Box 149, Folder 7)
    - Messages from the Governor, 1989 November-September (Box 149, Folder 8)
    - Messages from the Governor, 1989 August-July (Box 150, Folder 1)
    - Messages from the Governor, 1989 June-May (Box 150, Folder 2)
    - Messages from the Governor, 1989 April (Box 150, Folder 3)
    - Messages from the Governor, 1989 March-January (Box 150, Folder 4)
    - [Messages from the Governor] - Certificates of Recognition, A-C (Box 150, Folder 5)
    - [Messages from the Governor] - Certificates of Recognition, D-H (Box 150, Folder 6)
    - [Messages from the Governor] - Certificates of Recognition, I-L (Box 150, Folder 7)
    - [Messages from the Governor] - Certificates of Recognition, M-O (Box 151, Folder 1)
    - [Messages from the Governor] - Certificates of Recognition, P-U (Box 151, Folder 2)
    - [Messages from the Governor] - Certificates of Recognition, V-Y (Box 151, Folder 3)
    - [Messages from the Governor] - Proclamations (Box 151, Folder 4)
    - [Messages from the Governor] - See Also State of the Commonwealth Address
    - Model General Assembly - YMCA (Box 151, Folder 5)
    - National Air and Space Museum Expansion (Box 151, Folder 6)
    - Other State Offices (Box 151, Folder 7)
    - Requests - Contribution (Box 151, Folder 8)
    - Requests - General (part one) (Box 151, Folder 9)
    - Requests - General (part two) (Box 152, Folder 1)
    - Requests - General (part three) (Box 152, Folder 2)
    - Resignations (Box 152, Folder 3)
    - Retirement Letters (Box 152, Folder 4)
    - Staff Correspondence (Leonard L. Hopkins, Jr., Chief of Staff), 1989 December 29-December 7 (Box 152, Folder 5)
    - Staff Correspondence (Leonard L. Hopkins, Jr., Chief of Staff), 1989 December 6-November 21 (Box 152, Folder 6)
    - Staff Correspondence (Leonard L. Hopkins, Jr., Chief of Staff), 1989 November 20-October 20 (Box 153, Folder 1)
    - Staff Correspondence (Leonard L. Hopkins, Jr., Chief of Staff), 1989 October 19-September 29 (Box 153, Folder 2)
    - Staff Correspondence (Andrew B. Fogarty, Chief of Staff), 1989 September 29-September 1 (Box 153, Folder 3)
    - Staff Correspondence (Andrew B. Fogarty, Chief of Staff), 1989 August 31-August 10 (Box 153, Folder 4)
    - Staff Correspondence (Andrew B. Fogarty, Chief of Staff), 1989 August 9-July 17 (Box 153, Folder 5)
    - Staff Correspondence (Andrew B. Fogarty, Chief of Staff), 1989 July 12-April 25 (Box 153, Folder 6)
    - Staff Correspondence (Andrew B. Fogarty, Chief of Staff), 1989 April 21-February 23 (Box 154, Folder 1)
    - Staff Correspondence (Andrew B. Fogarty, Chief of Staff), 1989 February 20-January 3 (Box 154, Folder 2)
    - State of the Commonwealth Address, 1989 January 11 and Correspondence (Box 154, Folder 3)
    - Sympathy Letters (Box 154, Folder 4)
    - Thank You Letters from the Governor (Box 154, Folder 5)
    - Thank You Letters to the Governor, 1989 December 20-June 22 (Box 154, Folder 6)
    - Thank You Letters to the Governor, 1989 June 20-January 9 (Box 154, Folder 7)
    - Virginia Cultural Laureates (Box 155, Folder 1)
    - Virginia Silver Star Foundation (Box 155, Folder 2)
    - List of 1989 Form Letters (Box 155, Folder 3)
    - Form Letter 89-1 (number not used)
    - Form Letter 89-2, Route 29/Charlottesville Bypass/Ivy Farms Homeowners Against (Box 155, Folder 4)
    - Form Letter 89-3, VSRS/Payment of Retiree Health Coverage (missing)
    - Form Letter 89-4, Against Mail Order Prescription (Box 155, Folder 5)
    - Form Letter 89-5, Prescription Drugs-Pharmacists (Box 155, Folder 6)
    - Form Letter 89-6, Route 29-Late Answer (Box 155, Folder 7)
    - Form Letter 89-7, Swans (Box 155, Folder 8)
    - Form Letter 89-8, Developmental Aides (Box 155, Folder 9)
    - Form Letter 89-9, Developmental Aides and Retirement Insurance (Box 155, Folder 10)
    - Form Letter 89-10, VSRS/Payment of Retiree Health Costs (Box 155, Folder 11)
    - Form Letter 89-11, Veterans' Home (Pro) (Box 155, Folder 12)
    - Form Letter 89-12, SB 727-Gun Control (Box 155, Folder 13)
    - Form Letter 89-13, Veterans' Home (Pro) No. 2 (Box 155, Folder 14)
    - Form Letter 89-14, State Veterans' Home (Box 155, Folder 15)
    - Form Letter 89-15, SB 727-Gun Control (Box 155, Folder 16)
    - Form Letter 89-16, SB 727-Gun Control (Box 155, Folder 17)
    - Form Letter 89-17, SB 727-Gun Control (Con) (Box 155, Folder 18)
    - Form Letter 89-18, SB 727-Gun Control (Pro) (Box 155, Folder 19)
    - Form Letter 89-19, Public School Nurses (Pro Additional Funding) (Box 155, Folder 20)
    - Form Letter 89-20, Back Bay Wildlife Refuge (Box 155, Folder 21)
    - Form Letter 89-21, Against Tolls on Coleman Bridge (Box 155, Folder 22)
    - Form Letter 89-22, After Decision-Coleman Bridge (Box 156, Folder 1)
    - Form Letter 89-23, Baby Care/School Nurses (Box 156, Folder 2)
    - Form Letter 89-24, Coalfields/Pittston Strike (Box 156, Folder 3)
    - Form Letter 89-25, Capital Punishment (Box 156, Folder 4)
    - Form Letter 89-26, Kiptopeke Site (Box 156, Folder 5)
    - Form Letter 89-27, Chesapeake Preservation Act (Box 156, Folder 6)
    - Form Letter 89-28, Chesapeake Bay Preservation Act (Support) (Box 156, Folder 7)
    - Form Letter 89-29, Coal Strike (Box 156, Folder 8)
    - Form Letter 89-30, Unsolved Murders (Box 156, Folder 9)
    - Form Letter 89-31, Confederate Home (Letter 2) (Box 156, Folder 10)
    - Form Letter 89-32, Chesapeake Bay Regulations-Thanks (Box 156, Folder 11)
    - Form Letter 89-33, Chesapeake Bay Regulations-Asking for Support (Box 156, Folder 12)
    - Form Letter 89-34, Coal Strike (Long Letter) (Box 156, Folder 13)
    - Form Letter 89-35, Church Street in Smithfield (Box 156, Folder 14)
    - Form Letter 89-36, Home for Needy Confederate Women (Letter 2) (Box 156, Folder 15)
    - Form Letter 89-37, Chesapeake Bay-Strengthen (Box 157, Folder 1)
    - Form Letter 89-38, Culpeper Prison Expansion (Box 157, Folder 2)
    - Form Letter 89-39, Coalfield-School Bus (Box 157, Folder 3)
    - Form Letter 89-40, Mentally Disabled (part one) (Box 157, Folder 4)
    - Form Letter 89-40, Mentally Disabled (part two) (Box 157, Folder 5)
    - Form Letter 89-41 (number not used? missing?)
    - Form Letter 89-42, Chesapeake Bay-Thanks to Governor (Box 157, Folder 6)
    - Form Letter 89-43, Flag Decision (Box 157, Folder 7)
    - Form Letter 89-44, Kim-Stan Landfill (Box 157, Folder 8)
    - Form Letter 89-45, Nursing Home Beds (Box 157, Folder 9)
    - Form Letter 89-46, Coalfields (Box 158, Folder 1)
    - Form Letter 89-47, Infant Blindness (Box 158, Folder 2)
    - Form Letter 89-48, Greekfest (Box 158, Folder 3)
    - Form Letter 89-49, Joe Girratano (Box 158, Folder 4)
    - Form Letter 89-50, Rails-to-Trails (Box 158, Folder 5)
  - Sub-Series E: Cabinet
    - E.1 - Secretary of Administration
    - Correspondence and Memorandums to Governor's Office, 1989 December 12-July 6 (Box 158, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence and Memorandums to Governor's Office, 1989 June 21-January 3 (Box 158, Folder 7)
    - Governor's Correspondence (Box 158, Folder 8)
    - Prescription Drugs (Box 158, Folder 9)
    - State Employee Benefits (Box 158, Folder 10)
    - State Employee Salaries (Box 158, Folder 11)
    - E.1 - Secretary of Administration - State Agencies
    - Compensation Board (Box 159, Folder 1)
    - Council on Information Management (Box 159, Folder 2)
    - Department of Employee Relations Counselors (Box 159, Folder 3)
    - Department of General Services (Box 159, Folder 4)
    - Department of Information Technology (Box 159, Folder 5)
    - Department of Personnel and Training (Box 159, Folder 6)
    - Department of Personnel and Training - Equal Employment Opportunity Commission (E.E.O.C.) (Box 159, Folder 7)
    - Department of Personnel and Training - Virginia Executive Institute (Box 159, Folder 8)
    - Department of Veterans' Affairs (Box 159, Folder 9)
    - State Board of Elections (Box 159, Folder 10)
    - Virginia Supplemental Retirement System (Box 159, Folder 11)
    - E.2 - Secretary of Economic Development